are you uh
hypnotizing me no i'm asking
well it was working well right sometimes
no sometimes it didn't it didn't
yeah
okay go more here this way let go the
left hand
left a little grip it now grip it you
keep the racket more over here like
don't put it this way
yeah put it more here this way
yeah especially
you're doing this especially in the back
you're going you're going like this so
it sets the wrist
it's usually something that can be okay
for you i don't like it because it makes
the wrist too rigid too stiff
and then end up like going like this and
you get underneath the ball racket face
opens up so i'd like you to be a little
bit more neutral
good job anna
think about
how i slipped somebody's head
yes
because it has to go up right but you're
going up already so i don't think you're
doing anything wrong right now
yeah that's well that's for more top
spin but right now it's okay just keep
keep doing that there you go
come again
all right stay here we're gonna feed you
some okay
good
okay remember let's let's go through it
one more time here hold the racket
what i don't want you to do is this as
you're taking the racket back
this is just for you it doesn't work i
like you to be this way more even when
you go here this way more now when you
accelerate forward
now you don't have to worry about your
wrist anymore it'll naturally go more
here
but you know what mark
my dance coach yeah invited me to see
tennis in march in miami oh this is
great anna i want you to go i want you
to go
now you might get recognized over there
seriously i told you listen dude you're
gonna be hanging out
i know you see how the forehead is
looking better yeah when i don't think
about that but well see but this is a
great example because like i started
talking about like stuff unrelated to
technique and all of a sudden you were
just talking and hitting you saw how
good that was
that's what i mean you don't have to
you pass the point of having to
overthink
just hit yeah yeah maybe on saturday
morning before cleaning i should have a
little bit of vodka to chill out
so i don't think about it
okay here we go
anna you're on fire right now
okay i'm jinxing you a little bit on
purpose too
i'll try to be quiet here we go
yeah be quiet please
okay i will
you can see
how terrible i am
here we go come on
no
okay say something all right all right
see now it's weird i'm not saying
anything right that's weird too
i remember when i used to train my dad
when he was quiet that was the worst
because i thought idea he was there's no
reference point then another that too
but it like it almost like i'm what is
why is he not saying anything is he
upset is he mad and that's like weird
you know
yeah so i do have to say stuff you see
come on
i need to understand which one was good
that's what i mean believe it or not
yeah i really do
that's why i keep saying good job when
you do a good job here we go
it's already said this a few times i
like you here as opposed to here yeah
because when you're here when you start
coming into the ball i feel like you're
like this you're like here and then
opening up the racket face a little bit
just like so stiff so rigid
here like the wrist is a little bit more
neutral don't worry i'll come back here
in a forward phase that's gonna happen
actually but i feel like you're more
natural this way and able to turn the
racket around the correct way on the on
the finish here we go come on
i love it yes
ana this is killer right now
that was again like this
and you know what else i noticed though
when you do this you get a lot less
power there's less depth
the ball goes a lot shorter and the
other side so you actually it takes the
power away
like this is straight yeah well listen
don't worry about topspin so much you
already have some top spin you don't
have to have the crazy top spin don't
worry about that just hit the forehand
normal you already when you go up here
like this you get natural topspin
now you might not get a heavy topspin
that's a completely different story
don't worry about that part okay
neutral as you take it back neutral
good ana
no good all the way back here fully
extended wrist on the take back come on
better and again
and uh this is crazy
very clean good net clearance come on
and again come
okay what do you think about that one
you like it
i
purposely step sideways too
that's fine don't worry about that you
can do that was it good
that that part is it was okay that's
okay
no not that much because again that was
just going to get your your feeling
about it because again was like one of
these four hands yes you did hit hard
and pretty decent but
again look this as you're taking it back
let's make that correction have the
wrist in a little bit more neutral
position as you're taking a racket back
you see what i mean like when you have
it like this there is more of an
effortlessness
but look how easy you hit it with no
effort and ball went very far
as opposed the other way where you're
like this the ball doesn't go anywhere
i'm notorious for over doing things you
know what it was i think where this
started happening i remember this this
has been happening for a while like when
you have a lack of control of contact
you like exaggerate and make the wrist
like locked in
very early on
so that you have more control here
i think that's why you're doing it
you make your wrist super rigid and over
over extended so that you have more
control of contact actually for some
people this might actually be a
corrective technique if they're too
sloppy here so this is kind of a
confusing thing that i'm correcting with
you because i would be okay with some
other players doing it but unfortunately
when you're like hype extended like this
there's other things happening where
you're
if you see if you went like this and
then came in like this this would be
fine because there's actually pro
players that take the racket back like
this
especially like female pro players and
they come in like this they're fine but
when you go like this i feel like you're
always kind of
in here like that
like the wrist
continues to open up on the bottom
portion of the shot
and if you get a bad angle here now
you're underneath the ball and they
start spraying and that's why for you
i'm making this correction just for you
oh that's only because my back hurts
i slept wrong and i have something back
here so i'm kind of like i can't really
i would love to slouch like i normally
do i would love to stand like this but
it hurts when i do that so it's much
better
oh is that right
that's crazy
very there's an effortlessness to that
forehand that i just love here we go
anna this is crazy
come on watch this one
it's okay it's all right yeah
anna you see this change now
yeah it's beautiful job the grip is not
bothering me as much anymore okay good
i like your body activity there here we
go
that one's too stiff
oh topspin in the house here we go come
and uh that was the old forehand
yes
yes i don't like it not a fan here we go
you see the difference
those two forehands compared well i know
you probably can't feel the difference
but i definitely see it in the way it
looks
it's the right way for you trust me
nice anna this is crazy what's going on
right now
a little too far away but i don't mind i
don't mind at all
anna look at your body action today very
nice all right let's work one more
forehand uh thing that
you have trouble with which is running
up and hitting a forehand now you
interestingly ask me about like going
like this
now don't be afraid to go like this this
is
not bad at all no you can step into the
forehand
that would be careful going that way
because you'll lock yourself in it's
more of a step forward on the forehand
but anytime anytime the ball is in front
of you anytime the ball does not have a
lot of penetration do not be afraid to
go like this
all right on the backhand you're going
to be hitting the majority of the
backhands that way there's got to be
some that you'll hit more open but you
know what the crazy thing about this
open closest you're already doing it
like correctly
because we never really forced any type
of stances so you're already doing it
correctly you're not thinking about you
doing both open and close yeah
so that's the best way to build the
which stance that you have is by not
not forcing any stances just letting it
happen naturally and now your
focus is not on the legs at all you
don't even know how you're hitting the
four and a half at the time that's
exactly what needs to know it needs to
have you get up to it
very clean and back to them back to the
middle here we go come
there lift it
it's all right
and again come on
good anna it's very clean right now
come
again good work i like it a lot no no i
like it a lot this is good
that was a dead ball right
you wanted to get it it was on purpose
correct
no
yes of course
all right here we go here we go anna
this happens sometimes
good right away you corrected it it's
beautiful
don't push like we see how careful and
how slow you made the contact
when the acceleration stops this is the
crazy thing about tennis when you start
slowing down this area here and you're
guiding the ball forward you're steering
it you see how long it goes it just
flies on you okay my footwork was not
i think that was enough
here we go now come on
very clean textbook here we go now
very clean anna come on
five more
here we go
four more come on
okay bring it around a little more come
on bring it around the body
yes don't be it's a little too too much
pace now don't be when the ball is low
like this and you're closer don't hit
too hard three more come on
better two more
okay last one
ten more anna this is the oldest trick
in the book here we go i'll give you a
couple of extra balls always come
out one more time come you can't miss
the last one go
no it's all
that's not bad go back you wanna do one
more i don't mind come on
it's all about reps so i might be
cheating on the reps i might be saying
five more end up being 15 more
it's just a trick because it's all about
you hitting as many forehands as
possible
nice work
good
good anna come
very strong forehand come on
okay come again
good anna
on the run
nice one
oh yes match point come
play it out
you got scared one more time move that
ball right there
you try to pass me
come on pass me anna
out
yes you got me there you're playing
better on the forehand you feel more
comfortable yeah
nice work yeah keep going that was this
is for your clinic
but this is the right way just keep
doing this this is the right way today
was maybe the best forehand day you had
in a while yeah
very nice good job